Register of the Charles Hill Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Increment received in 2002 (Box 106)
  - Notebook on the Middle East (in original order) (Box 111)
    - Maps
      - Israel-Jordan Jerusalem administration
      - Syria administrative divisions
      - Jordan administrative divisions
      - Golan Heights, Syria
      - United Arab Republic
      - Camp David
      - Egypt
      - Israeli occupied West Bank
      - Israel – Fighter aircraft bases
      - Middle East
      - Western Turkey
      - Southwestern Saudi Arabia
      - Kuwait, parts of Iraq, Iran
      - United Arab Emirates, Bahrain, Qatar
      - Oman
      - Yemen, South Yemen
      - Tel Aviv
      - Nazareth
      - Saudi Arabia
      - Saudi Arabia, Iran
      - Indian Ocean
    - Areas of control, Beirut, Lebanon, August 1978
    - Lebanon
    - Text of United Nations Security Council Resolution 242, November 22, 1967
    - Newspaper article "Menachem Begin: The Person, the Policy,", 1978
    - Chart on Foreign Military Sales Financing Program, 1955-1977, with notes by Charles Hill
    - Chart on Foreign Military Sales Financing Program, Israel, 1955-1978
    - Chart on Commercial Exports (FY 1960-1977)
    - Chart on Foreign Military Sales Deliveries (FY 1950-1977)
    - Chart on Foreign Military Sales Agreements (FY 1950-1977)
    - Report on the Middle East Peace Process, October 15, 1981
  - Subject file – United Nations. (Box 114-115)
    See also Box 104
    Drafts of chapters from UNvanquished: The United States versus the United Nations, 1999, by Boutros Boutros-Ghali.
- Increment received in 2003 (Box 116)
  - Biographical file
    - Biographical sketches
    - Calling cards
    - Career files
    - Clippings
    - Gates family genealogy
    - Inventory of 30 Institute Place
    - Miscellany
    - Poetry of Katie Hill, age 5
    - Printed matter
  - Correspondence (Box 117)
    - General, 1958-2001
    - Barker, Richard, 1959-1960
    - Brown, William A., 1981
    - Bunker, Ellsworth, 1971
    - Chadwick, Beatty, 1960-1962
    - Cumberland County, New Jersey, 1961-1962
    - Doherty, William P., Jr., 1960
    - Evans, Joseph, 1960
    - Hatcher, John, 1961
    - Hill, Emily, undated
    - Hill family, primarily Charlie and Martha to and from Charlie's parents, Morton and Alvenia Hill, undated-1973
    - Hill family, 1976-1982 (Box 118)
    - Hoover Institution, 1993-1999
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1976
      (copy)
    - Nixon, Richard, 1985
    - Reagan, Ronald, 1982
    - Shultz, George P., 1982-1999
    - State of New Jersey, 1961-1962
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1960-1962
  - Brown University file, 1953-1957
    - College papers
    - Printed matter
  - University of Pennsylvania file, 1958-1961 (Box 119)
    - Class notes, including notes of Martha Hill
    - College papers (Box 120)
    - Miscellany (Box 121)
    - Printed matter
  - Foreign Service – Department of State file, 1961-1989
    - General
      - Biographical file
        - General
        - Appointment
        - Printed matter
      - Office files
      - Speeches and writings
    - Zurich, 1963
    - Taiwan, 1964-1965 (Box 122)
    - Hong Kong, 1966-1969
      - General
        - Information on the February coup
        - Miscellany
        - Notebook of Charles Hill
        - Office file
        - Printed matter
      - Chinese studies
        - Background notes
          - Language
          - Notes
          - Printed matter
        - T'ai-Chi Ch'uan
  - Harvard, Research Fellow in East Asian Studies file, 1970 (Box 123)
    - General
      - Class lists
      - Miscellany
      - Printed matter
      - University assignments
    - Correspondence
    - East Asian Studies class notes
      - Chinese language
      - Chinese literature
      - Chinese painting
      - Economic development in China and Japan
      - Republican China
      - Social structure of China and Japan
      - U.S. and East Asia
  - Vietnam file, 1971-1973 (Box 124)
    - Biographical file
      - Career records
      - Passport
      - Scrapbook (incomplete) and scrapbook pages
    - Office file
      - Memoranda
      - Miscellany
      - Notes/notebook
      - Printed matter
        - General
        - Background information
        - "Boundary Concepts and Practices in Southeast Asia"
        - "Cease-fire," Time, 1973 February 5
        - "Diplomatic and Consular List", 1972
        - "Documents Relating to the War Power of Congress...,", 1970 July
        - "Escalating in a Quagmire" by Daniel Ellsberg, 1970
        - "Guide to Living in Saigon" (Box 125)
        - "Gulf of Tonkin, 1964 Incidents,", 1968
        - "Hanoi and South Vietnam's 'Liberation Front'"
        - "How Could Vietnam Happen?" by James C. Thompson, Jr., 1968
        - "Impact of the War in Southeast Asia on the U.S. Economy,", 1970
        - "Legislation on the Indochina War,", 1971
        - "My Visit to the Liberated Zones of South Vietnam" by Wilfred Burchett, 1966
        - "Perspective on Asia: The New U.S. Doctrine and Southeast Asia,", 1969
        - "President Ho-Chi-Minh,", 1966
        - "Realites vietnamiennes,", 1966
        - "Restoring Peace in Viet-nam,", 1973
        - "Review of the Vietnam Conflict and Its Impact on U.S. Military Commitments Abroad,", 1968
        - "Saigon Streets" by Doan Bich, 1967
        - "South Vietnam: Background Data,", 1973
        - "South Vietnam: Provincial Maps,", 1971
          (2 copies)
        - "Tactical Aerodrome Directory: South Vietnam,", 1971
        - "Thailand, Laos, and Cambodia: January 1972," (Box 126)
        - "Thong Bao" Special "Tet" Edition, 1972
        - "United States Involvement in Southeast Asia,", 1970
        - "U.S. Assistance Programs in Vietnam,", 1972
        - U.S. Government Agencies Vietnam Telephone Directory, 1971
        - "U.S. Heroin Problem and Southeast Asia,", 1973
        - "VC-NVA Employment of Mines & Booby Traps,", 1970
        - "Vietnam: December 1969,", 1970
        - "Vietnam: May 1972,"
        - Vietnam Archive: Holdings as of April 1, 1998
        - Vietnam Post Reports, 1967, 1971
        - Vietnamese Basic Course, Volume 1
      - Reports
        - "Lessons from China" Kiangsi, 1934
        - "A Strategy for Counter-Subversion," Vietnam, 1966
      - Speeches by Ambassador Ellsworth Bunker
      - Subject file
        - An Loc battle, 1972 April-July
        - Miscellany
        - Vietnamese communication
  - Policy Planning Staff file, 1974-1979 (Box 127)
    - Biographical file
      - Clippings
      - Correspondence
      - Miscellany
    - Speeches and writings
      - "Middle East Peace Process"
      - Speech drafts for Henry Kissinger
        - Fortune magazine dinner, 1975 November 25
        - "America and the World," Time Magazine's series of Bicentennial Essays, 1975 December 9
    - Office file
      - Course on diplomacy
      - Memoranda
      - Miscellany
      - Organization chart
      - Printed matter
      - Schedules
      - Speech writing file
    - Subject file
      - Agency for International Communication (proposed)
      - Bunker, Ellsworth
      - Ford, Gerald
      - Hatch Act, [1939]
      - Kissinger, Henry
  - Secretary of State Office file (Box 128)
    - Biographical file
      - Career file
      - Clippings
      - Executive Secretary plaque (photocopy)
      - Miscellany
      - Notes/booklists
    - Correspondence – Elsie Haley
    - Map of Department of State offices
    - Secretary George P. Shultz file
      - Clippings
      - Memoranda
      - Miscellany
      - Schedules
      - Speeches
    - Secretary's Library file
    - Subject file (Box 129)
      - Alfalfa Club
      - Chevening
      - Corregidor
      - Diplomatic Reception Rooms
      - Education
      - Miscellany
      - Nicaragua
    - Travel file
      - Asia, 1984
      - Iceland, 1987
      - Israel, 1987
      - Soviet Union for Konstantin Chernenko's funeral, 1985
      - Soviet Union, 1987
      - Switzerland, 1985
  - Hoover Institution/United Nations/Yale University file, 1992-Present (Box 130)
    - Biographical file
      - Clippings
      - Travel
    - Correspondence
    - Speeches and writings
      - General
        - Calendar
          - 1992
          - 1993
          - 1994
          - 1995
          - 1996
          - 1997
        - Notebooks, 1990 March – 1998 October (Box 131)
      - Letter to the editor, New York Review of Books, 1997 (Box 132)
      - "NATO Strategy for a New Generation," Hoover Newsletter, 1997
      - "A Millennium Year Peace for the Middle East?", 1999
      - "Why Should We Care About East Timor? The Large Scale Significance of a Small-Scale Crisis,", 1999
    - Subject file
      - Habib, Phil
      - Miscellany
      - Shultz, George
      - Thucydides
  - Audio-visual file (Box 133)
    - Photographs
      - 20 family prints, including prints of Christopher Van Lieu with Emily Van Lieu, Charles Hill, Norma Thompson, 2 prints of Katie Hill, 1 print of Laura Van Lieu
        (#1)
      - 1 print of refugees in Manchuria, 1960s?
        (#2)
      - 2 prints of Charles Sanders Pierce house
        (#3)
      - 2 copies of print of book jacket for Letter from Grosvenor Square by John Gilbert Winant
        (#4)
      - 1 print of Larry Klayman and Bob Barr
        (#5)
      - 6 prints of Martha Mitchell Hill, 1 print of Charles Hill and others, 1 print of Morton Hill (Charles' father)
        (#6)
      - 10 family prints with Charles and Martha Hill, Morton and Alvenia Hill, and others, 1963
        (#7)
      - 19 prints, Taiwan, 1964
        (#8)
      - 1 print of Charles Hill and graduating class, Basic Foreign Service Officers' Course Class, 1962
        (#9)
      - 3 prints of departure of Charles and Martha Hill from San Francisco to Taiwan; 23 prints, Taiwan, 1965
        (#10)
      - 35 prints of Saigon, Bangkok, Vientiane, 1966-1969
        (#11)
      - 10 prints, Vietnam: 1 of Charles Hill, Ellsworth Bunker, and others; 3 of Ellsworth Bunker and others; 1 of Charles Hill and others; 1 of Ellsworth Bunker and others, 1967; 2 of outdoor scenes; 1 of Jane Fonda in Hanoi, 1972; 1 of unidentified woman, Anti-Aircraft Watch Post, North Vietnam
        (#12)
      - 2 prints of Charles Hill, Henry Kissinger, and others, Policy Planning Staff, ca. 1975
        (#13)
      - 1 print of Charles Hill and others at costume party in Israel, 1979
        (#14)
      - Department of State: 1 print of battleship, 1981; 1 print of Charles Hill, George Shultz, Andrei Gromyko, and others, 1985; 1 print of Charles Hill, Ronald Reagan, and others on airplane; 1 print of Charles Hill, George Shultz, and unidentified person in Shultz's office; 1 print of Charles Hill shaking hands with Yitzhak Shamir, with George Shultz and two others also in print; photocopy of print of Charles Hill and Ronald Reagan; 14 prints of China trip, 1987
        (#15)
      - 8 family prints, 1965-1972
        (#16)
      - 1 Shultz family Christmas card, 1992
        (#17)
      - 5 miscellaneous prints
        (#18)
      - 1 print of Charles Hill, approximately age 4
        (#19)
  - Maps (Box 134)
    - Africa
    - Atlantic Ocean
    - Beijing
    - Beijing streets
    - Beijing Temple of Heaven
    - Beijing tourist map
    - Cambridge, Massachusetts
    - China in maps
    - China - Mainland
    - China – Standard Atlas of the Republic of China
    - China, Japan, Korea, Southeast Asia, Australia, Tibet
      (folder with 25 maps)
    - Iceland
    - Iolani Palace, Honolulu, Hawaii
    - Kowloon Peninsula
    - Laos
    - Lisbon
    - Madrid
      (2 maps)
    - Manila
    - Reykjavik, Iceland
    - Saigon and vicinity
    - South Vietnam
    - Switzerland, Austria, and Northern Italy
    - Taipei
    - Taiwan
    - Tokyo and Yokohama
    - Vienna
    - Vietnam
    - Vietnam III Military Region
    - Vietnam, Cambodia, Laos, and Thailand
    - Zurich
  - Oversize memorabilia (Box 135)
    - Maps
      - China railroads
      - China Sea
      - Taichung, Taiwan
      - Vietnam – Operational Navigation Chart
      - Vietnam – Tactical Pilotage Chart
      - Vietnam – U.S. Air Force Pilotage Chart
    - Program from the 204th Commencement, University of Pennsylvania, 1960 June 15
    - China Pictorial, 1983
    - Certificate of appreciation, Venice Economic Summit, Rome, The Vatican, West Berlin, and Bonn, June 3-12, 1987, from Ronald Reagan
    - Certificate of appreciation, Helsinki Moscow Summit, and London, 1988 May 25-June 3, from Ronald Reagan
    - Certificate of appreciation, NATO Summit, Brussels, 1988 March 1-3, from Ronald Reagan
    - Certificate of appreciation, Indonesia/ASEAN Conference and the Tokyo Economic Summit, 1986 April 25-May 7, from Ronald Reagan
    - Certificate of appreciation, Quebec City, Canada, 1985 March 17-18, from Ronald Reagan
    - Certificate of appreciation, Ottawa, Canada, 1987 April 5-6, from Ronald Reagan
    - Certificate of appreciation, Reykjavik, Iceland, from Ronald Reagan
    - Certificate of appreciation, Lebanon Working Group, 1982 June 6-September 3, from George P. Shultz
    - Certificate of appreciation, Bonn Economic Summit, Spain, the European Parliament, and Portugal, 1985 April 30-May 10, from Ronald Reagan
    - Flight certificate certifying that Charles Hill flew on Air Force One as a guest of Ronald Reagan, 1985 April 30
    - 2 certificates of survival, 1980 May 18 and 1981 May 10
    - Poster for a roundtable discussion with Charles Hill as a participant, [2002] October 14
    - Scrapbook, 1955-1957
    - Print of U.S. Mission Council, Saigon, Vietnam, 1973 January
    - Superior Honor Award (framed) to Charles Hill for serving as Executive Secretary of the U.S. Mission in Vietnam from April 1972 to February 1973, 1973 May
  - Memorabilia (Box 136)
    - Map indicating Charles Hill's and Arthur Cates' location and phone number in Saigon
    - Certificate, The Medal for Civilian Service in Vietnam, signed by Ellsworth Bunker, 1972 February 17
    - 12 reproductions of scenes in Portugal
    - Booklet from the State Jewish Museum in Prague
    - Calling cards, Charles Hill, Counselor for Political Affairs, Israel
    - Passport, 1978-1983
    - Invitations, 1985-1986
    - Medal of Pope Paul II from the Vatican, 1984
    - Identity tags, 1985
    - Parking permit, 1988
    - Department of State 10-year pin
    - Christmas greeting with 1952 rabbit pin
    - "Back Bunker" pin
    - List of code names, Vietnam
    - Thank you plaque of appreciation, Geneva Summit, 1985, signed by Ronald Reagan
    - Brochures from the Embassy of the United States of America in Mexico; U.S. Embassy, Canberra; Aqaba; Palace Museum, Beijing
    - Booklet about the SS Constitution, 1961
    - Notice of talk by Charles Hill, "The Middle East: Grand Strategy's Greatest Challenge"
    - International Security Studies, Yale University, 2002 October 9
    - Copy of address to the United Nations General Assembly, signed by George Shultz, 1987
    - Certificate, Executive Secretariat Hall of Fame for Extraordinary Service Rendered by Charles Hill, 1987 February 11
    - Folder from Secretary of State George Shultz's Visit to Berlin, 1985 December 14-15
    - Briefcase from visit to Reykjavik, 1987 June 11-12
    - Unidentified brown leather folder
- Increment received in 2005 (Box 137)
  - Biographical file
    - General
      - Appointment calendars, 1960-1977; telephone number lists, 1980's
      - Biographical sketches
      - Biography
        - Material collected by Charles Hill
        - Molly Worthen biography – two sections
      - Clippings
      - Drawings by Martha Hill (Box 138)
      - Miscellany
      - Obituary, written by Charles Hill
    - Boyhood
      - Clippings on New Jersey birthplace of Charles Hill
      - Hill family cottage
      - Newspapers collected by Hill family
    - Education (Box 139)
      - High school graduation program
      - Brown University clippings
      - University of Pennsylvania Law School printed matter
      - Harvard University East Asian Studies directory
    - Career files
      - Foreign Service records
      - Baylor University offer of position (Box 140)
      - Miscellany
      - Stanford Travel/Study program
  - Correspondence (Box 141)
    - General
      - undated
      - 1956
      - 1957
      - 1958
      - 1959
      - 1983
      - 1985
      - 1989
      - 1990
      - 1991
      - 1992
      - 1993
      - 1994
      - 1996
      - 1997
      - 1999
      - 2000
      - 2001
      - 2002
      - 2003
      - 2004
    - Collected (Box 142)
      - Dole, Robert, to George Shultz, 1991
      - Thompson, Norma, to the Editor, 1991
    - General
    - Drafts by Charles Hill
    - Barker, R.C., 1958
    - Barnes, Harry G., Jr., 1991
    - Campbell, Tom, 1991
    - Cozza, Carm, 1996
    - Drachkovitch, Milorad, 1991
    - Gandhi, Gopalkrishna, 1991
    - Glover, Gordon, 1959
    - Graze, Debi, 1989-1990
    - Hill, C. Morton and Alvenia, 1964-1991
    - Hill, Emily, 1985-2004
    - Hill, Katie, 1990-1993
    - Hill, Martha, 1990-1992
    - Hoover Institution, 1991
    - Hull, Cordell, 1991
    - Invest-in-America Council, 1991
    - Jewish organizations and groups, 1991
    - Kney-Tal, Harry, 1991
    - LaFeber, Walter, 1990-1991
    - Metzger, Tom, 1995
    - Palmer, Meridith, 1989-1991
    - Reed, Joseph Verner, 1996-2004
    - Reedy, Clyde, 2003-2004
    - Rothstein, Nicole, 1991
    - Seitz, Raymond G.H., 1991
    - Shultz, George, 1991-2004
    - Smith, George L., Jr., 1991 (Box 143)
    - Sofaer, Abraham, 1991
    - Stanford University invitations, etc., 1991
    - Thompson, Norma, 1989-1992
    - United States Institute of Peace, 1991
    - Vogel, Ezra, 1991
    - Wisner, Frank, 1991
  - Speeches and writings
    - List of notebook dates, 1978-1989
    - Notebooks
      - 1968
      - 1972-73
      - 1978-80
      - July 22, September 22-23; October 8, 16, 1997; September 16, October 27, November 4, 7, 1998; October 1, 1999; January 20, 2000 (Box 144)
      - April 10 - July 17, 1998
      - July 18 – December 10, 1998
      - December 8, 1998 – February 4, 1999
      - February 5 – April 4, 1999
      - April 5 – June 30, 1999
      - July 1 – October 31, 1999
      - November 1, 1999 – March 23, 2000 (Box 145)
      - March 23 – June 24, 2000
      - June 3-9; June 25-July 2; July 13- September 20, 2000
      - September 21, 2000 – January 31, 2001
      - February 1 – June 30; August 1-12, 2001
      - August 13 – December 31, 2001
      - January 1 – April 24, 2002
      - April 24 – June 30; August 1 – September 18, 2002
      - July 3-31, 2002 (Box 146)
      - August 29-30; September 19 – December 31, 2002
      - January 1 – April 28, 2003
      - April 28 – August 13, 2003
      - August 14, 2003 – January 22, 2004
      - January 23 – May 31, 2004
      - June 1 – August 16, 2004
    - Draft for George Shultz, "The Arab-Israeli Conflict,", undated (Box 147)
    - "A Fact-Based Initiative,", undated
    - Notes on "How I Learned About Vietnam" by Henry Kissinger, undated
    - Notes on National Portrait Gallery, undated
    - Paper on the "Marriage Ceremony" for American Civilization class, Brown University, undated
    - Draft on the Puritans, undated
    - Miscellaneous notes and printed matter
    - Notes from English 42, Brown University, undated
    - Brunonian, published by Alpha Delta Phi, Brown University, Spring 1956
    - Notes, University of London, 1956
    - Notes, Office of Voluntary Defender, Philadelphia, 1958
    - Letter to The Nation, January 17, 1976
    - Miscellaneous notes, printed matter, ca. 1987
    - "Man Thinking," American Studies International, April 1990
    - "Tales of the U.N.,", November 9, 1990
    - Draft on William Stanton, May 13, 1991
    - "Questions on Korea,", June 12, 1991
    - "Black Athena,", August 25, 1991
    - Draft on China-Taiwan, September 17, 1991
    - Outline for Stanford Five Minutes, September 25, 1991
    - Notes on Elliott Abrams, November 14, 1991
    - Hoover Institution India Project, 1992 (Box 148)
    - Letter to New York Review of Books, July 15, 1993
    - "Changing Political Moment,", November 14, 1994
    - "United States vs. United Nations,", January 13, 1997
    - Notes for talk at the University of Chicago, January 13, 1997
    - Notes on "Asia in the Global Security System" Harvard, April 11, 1997
    - Notes on lectures, conferences, Yale University, August 30, 1997 – April 30, 1999
    - Aide-memoir on International Security Studies at Yale, August 10, 1997
    - Failure of post-Cold War policies; printed matter, February 14, 1998
    - Prospectus for book on Vietnam, 1999
    - Draft on "Accountability" with George Shultz, 1999
    - Research materials on accountability, 5 folders, 1999
    - Notes, printed matter on scandals, 1999
    - Review essay on In the Stream of History by Warren Christopher, Political Science Quarterly, Summer 1999
    - Notes on East Timor, September 13, 1999
    - Letter to the Wall Street Journal, December 23, 1999
    - Notes on H.M.S. Brokendoor, ca. 2000 (Box 149)
    - "Follow the Flag," Hoover Digest, 2000
    - "Future of the U.N.,", September 7, 2000
    - "Power is Power Perceived,", September 15, 2000
    - "Wen Ho-Lee,", September 18, 2000
    - Notes and printed matter, 2001
    - "Humanitarian Intervention,", February 12, 2001
    - "Europeanization of America," Hoover Digest, Spring 2001
    - "Grand Strategy Project,", April 5-8, 2001
    - Notes, June 13, 2001
    - Lectures draft, June 22, 2001
    - Notes, December 21, 2001
    - Notes on "Papers of U.N. Secretary-General Boutros Boutros-Ghali,", 2002
    - "Ralph Bunche,", January 2002
    - "Teaching Grand Strategy,", February 15, 2002
    - "Strength and Diplomacy," Financial Times, April 11, 2002
    - "How to Get an Accountable Palestinian State,", June 5, 2002
    - "Iraq: After Victory, What?," memo to Condoleezza Rice from George Shultz, Harry Rowen, Charles Hill, July 29, 2002
    - Notes, printed matter on the economy, August 6, 2002
    - "Iraq: Act Now,", September 2, 2002
    - "Iraq: the U.N.'s Moment,", September 9, 2002
    - "Middle East: Grand Strategy's Major Challenge,", October 9, 2002
    - "Conversations on Iraq: the Case for Military Intervention,", October 21, 2002
    - Interview on the war in Iraq, AllLearn Program, October 30, 2002
    - "Vietnam,", November 13, 2002
    - Law School debate, December 11, 2002
    - "Milton's Paradise Lost as Grand Strategy,", December 24, 2002
    - Notes, printed matter, 2003
    - Niebuhr Forum on Religion and Public Life, 2003
    - "The Question Now Is: Who Lost Europe?,", February 17, 2003
    - "Love and War,", February 26, 2003
    - "Operation Iraqi Freedom," Hartford Courant, March 2003
    - "Teach-In," Yale University, March 26, 2003
    - Charles Hill quote, Khilafah Magazine, May 2003
    - "Kissinger as Memoirist,", May 29, 2003
    - Talking points for George Shultz, June, 2003 (Box 150)
    - Comments on Newt Gingrich's approach to State Department and Foreign Service, June 27, 2003
    - Message to Elliott Abrams, July 4, 2003
    - "A World of Opportunity and a World of Danger" draft for George Shultz, July 10, 2003
    - "Grand Strategy Extravaganza,", July 23, 2003
    - "Which Is Greatest: Philosophy, History, Political Theory, or Literature?", July 23, 2003
    - "Journey with Maps,", July 28, 2003
    - "Lessons of History," Canadian Journal of International Affairs, July 29, 2003
    - "Distant Lands, Shared History," Wall Street Journal, July 31, 2003
    - Notes on lunch with Henry Kissinger, August 16, 2003
    - Book draft on terrorism, with George Shultz, August 21, 2003
    - "Islamist War on the International System," Israel Journal, Fall 2003
    - "Remembering and Defending the International States System," International Journal, Autumn 2003
    - "Unreasonable Doubt,", December 29, 2003
    - Notes, printed matter, 2004